Guide to the Gwilym A. Price Papers, 1917-1983 AIS.2008.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Scrapbooks, 1940-1970; VII.
  - Scrapbook, 1963-64 (Box 10, Volume 2)
    Scrapbook documents the final years of Price's tenure at Westinghouse Electric, including newsclippings from Price's award from the American Society of Tool and Manufacturing Engineers, his chairmanship of Pennsylvania Science Council, his attendance at the Time Magazine Cover Banquet, news articles about the Westinghouse annual report, a script and note from the producer of the program "Space Age Success Formula" (KDKA/Westinghouse Broadcasting), and letters and news articles about his retirement from Westinghouse and from Allegheny Conference on Community Development. It also documents his continued involvement with colleges and universities, including his attendance at a dinner for supporters of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and a copy of "Development of the University of Pittsburgh Since WWII," for which Price was interviewed. Price's involvement in Republican politics is documented with a letter of thanks from Eisenhower for Price's help with his 73rd Birthday Party and an invitation to a White House dinner.
  - Scrapbook, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Volume 1)
    Scrapbook contains items from Price's continued time on the University of Pittsburgh Board of Trustees, including a note relaying his election as Chairman in 1966, materials from the dedication of the Van De Graff Accelerator Laboratory and the cornerstone laying ceremonies of the Johnstown campus, as well as Price's letter announcing his retirement from the board and the letters of congratulations he received. There is some personal correspondence with friends and family, as well as materials from the Design in Steel Awards Dinner, at which Price spoke.
  - Scrapbook, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Volume 2)
    Scrapbook largely contains materials about Price's personal and professional life from 1968-1970, though there are some earlier items. There is a 1908 clipping on the reorganization of Westinghouse, with letter from the Vice President of the General Cable Corporation, Price's Officer's Record Book from his time in the armed services (1918), and photos from University of Pittsburgh (pre-1968). Other post-1968 items from the University of Pittsburgh include a program from the dedication of the Johnstown Campus of the University of Pittsburgh, a letter confirming receipt of a Mellon Grant ($1 million) to fund the school of engineering at the University of Pittsburgh, letter the Gwilym A. Price Engineering Lectures, and a program from the dedication of Stanton Chapman Crawford Hall. There is also documentation of Price's continued work with the Republican party, including a letters of appreciation from Richard M. Nixon regarding his presidential run and fundraising for his campaign, a letter about Nixon from Pennsylvania governor Raymond Shafer, post-election communication from the Nixon campaign, and an invitation and program for an evening at the White House with Red Skelton. Price continued to do civic work, documented here by Price's letter to assist the fundraising campaign for the Crafton Methodist Church, and a program and clipping from The Greater Pittsburgh Guild for the Blind's Medallion Ball. There are also personal notes from friends and colleagues, including the Secretary of the Treasury; a letter about Price's resignation from his position at Radio Free Europe, and photos of Price's Anacosti (Canada) fishing trip in 1969.
- Speeches, 1939-c1973; VIII.
  This series contains typed copies of Price's speeches and presentations given to various corporate, civic, and professional organizations. In addition to the typed speeches, many folders contain related drafts, notes, correspondence, charts, programs, or reports. When exact titles for speeches and presentations are known, the title is enclosed in "quotations." When titles are not known, a descriptive title is provided in [brackets].
  - "The New South," [Pittsburgh People's Trust Company], 1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Speech on German War Reparations], Future Power Market Forum, February 17, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "The Outlook for 1949," Westinghouse Electric Stockholders Meeting, April, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Vital Difference" [speech on American capitalist democracy], Southeastern Electric Exchange, April 16, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "The Business Outlook and Westinghouse," Philadelphia Bond Club, April 28, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Speech at Dedication of Turbine Generator, Toledo, OH], Toledo Edison Company, April 29, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - [Speech on financial situation of Westinghouse Electric], to unknown group, June 6, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [Speech on relationship between government and private business], to unknown group, October 20, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Citadels of Capitalism," Third Annual Conference of Correspondent Banks, November 16, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Remarks at Dedication of Turbine Generator," Cincinnati Gas and Electric Company, December 10, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Is the Fair Deal Endangering the American Way of Life?," Philadelphia Bulletin Forum, March 21, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - [Speech on Westinghouse Electric's performance in 1950 and projected growth], Westinghouse Electric Stockholders Meeting, April 18, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - [Speech on Westinghouse Electric's performance, future, and government relations], Westinghouse Veterans Employees Association, January 30, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Can the Democracies Hang Together?," Pittsburgh Chapter of the Atlantic Union Committee, February 16, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Human Values in Industrial Civilization," Conference on Living in Industrial Civilization, May 17, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "Industry's Responsibility in Mobilization," Trust Section of the Pittsburgh Bankers Association, June 5, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "The Commissar and the Businessman," Economic Club of Chicago, October 4, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "The Commissar and the Businessman," Alabama State Chamber of Commerce, November 16, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - [Speech on government regulation of industry], to unknown group, February 14, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "The University in a Free Industrial Society," Johns Hopkins University, February 21, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - [Speech on Westinghouse Electric's performance in 1951 and projected growth], to unknown group of press, February 26, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "What a Company Looks for in Studying Possible Plant Locations," Boston, MA Chamber of Commerce, March 19, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - [Remarks at] Walter C. Beckjord Station Dedication, Cincinnati Gas and Electric Company, June 12, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "The Industrial Outlook for the Pittsburgh Area," Allegheny Conference on Community Development Annual Meeting, September 15, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - "The Great American Man Hunt," Carnegie Institute of Technology Alumni Dinner Meeting, October 9, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - "Westinghouse and Unions: The Case for Cooperation," International Union of Electrical Workers, October 10, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - [Response on the receiving an award] from the Western Pennsylvania Chapter of the Society of Industrial Realtors, October 30, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - "Presentation of 4-H Electric Program Scholarships," 4-H Club Congress, December 2, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - [Remarks on Westinghouse Electric's work in atomic energy], to group of industry leaders, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - [Remarks to members of Westinghouse Electric management in Mansfield and Lima, Ohio], 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - [Remarks accepting the William R. Hopkins Medal], St. David's Society of New York, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Management's Number One Job," National Industrial Conference Board, January 15, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - [Remarks at the Sixth Annual Banquet of Centennial Lodge No. 544 and La Fayette Lodge No. 652], January 24, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - "Changing Nature of Management's Responsibility," Diamond Jubilee Convention of the Case Institute of Technology, April 11, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - "A Problem and a Promise," Sales Managers Association of Philadelphia Annual Banquet, April 23, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - "Free World's First Line of Defense," Society of Naval Engineers Annual Banquet, May 1, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - [Speech on economic revitalization of the southern United States], Gateway Center, Pittsburgh, May 1953 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - "The Outlook for 1999," National Convention of the Building Owners and Managers Association, June 8, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - "A Pattern for the Power Industry," Dedication of the Meramec Plant of the Union Electric Company, St. Louis, MO, June 10, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "Forty Three Years of Suggestion Activities," National Association of Suggestion Systems Annual Convention, October 26, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - "Engineering America's Future," American Society of Mechanical Engineers Annual Dinner, December 2, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - [Outline for lecture at a Westinghouse management course], 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - [Remarks at the Charter Banquet of the Junior Chamber of Commerce of Chartiers Valley], February 26, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - [Outline of remarks to the Westinghouse Management Council], March 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - "What Does it Take to be Liberal?" and rebuttal of remarks made by Charles P. Taft, Philadelphia Bulletin Forum, March 10, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - "The Centennial Jubilee," Southeastern Electric Exchange, March 22, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - "Vicksburg [Mississippi] Plant Dedication Address", May 5, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - [Remarks made at the McGraw-Hill Westinghouse Dinner], May 24, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - "The Independent College in a Free Industrial Society: A Graduation Day Address," Transylvania College, June 7, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - [Remarks at Shippingsport Atomic Power Station ground breaking ceremony], September 6, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - "Westinghouse: Present Performance, Future Objectives," New York Society of Security Analysts, September 14, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - "The Atom and Electricity," American Bankers Association, October 20, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - [Remarks at Ohio Edison Company Power Plant Dedication], October 21, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - "The Centennial Jubilee of Light," Diamond Light Jubilee, October 21, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - [Introductory remarks for William A. Patterson], Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce, November 29, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - [Remarks at Houston Chamber of Commerce], December 1, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - [Statement on H.R. 1], Ways and Means Committee, U.S. House of Representatives, January 27, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - [Remarks on the dedication of Westinghouse Electric's development laboratory], March 1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - [Remarks on H.R. 1], Finance Committee, U.S. Senate, March 8, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Commencement address, Adrian College, June 5, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - [Introduction for speakers and closing remarks], Air Attaches Dinner, September 2, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - "The Atomic Era is Right Now," Dedication of the Bay Shore Station of the Toledo Edison Company, October 4, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - [Remarks at dedication of Westinghouse Electric's Raleigh, North Carolina plant], October 6, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - [Remarks at the President's Committee on Government Contracts], October 25, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - [Introduction of the film "Dawn's Early Light"], Southern Company Meeting, November 18, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - "Atomic Power and its Peacetime Industrial Uses," Award Dinner of the Society for Advancement of Management, Duquesne University Chapter, February 8, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - "Who Benefits from Automation?," Edison Electric Institute Sales Meeting, March 29, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - "Statement to Stockholders," Westinghouse Electric Corporation Stockholders Meeting, April 4, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - [Introductory remarks for Lt. Gen. C.B. Irvine], Foreign Air Attaches Dinner, August 31, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - "The Role of Research in our Society," and other prepared remarks from the Dedication of the Westinghouse Research Laboratory, September 20, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - "The Westinghouse Report for 1955: Annual Report to Supervisors", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - [Speech on civic life in Pittsburgh], Crafton Methodist Church Men's Club, February 17, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - [Speech on Westinghouse Electric's expansion in Athens, Georgia], Piedmont Driving Club, February 26, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - "Remarks by Gwilym A. Price at the Ground-Breaking Ceremonies in Athens, Georgia", February 26, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - [Speech on the selection of Athens for Westinghouse's expansion], Georgia Center for Continuing Education, Athens, February 26, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [Speech on industrial growth in the southern United States], Mountain Brook Club, Birmingham, Alabama, February 27, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - [Remarks on the importance of science education], Sixteenth Annual Science Talent Search, March 11, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Our Mutual Stake in Industrial Research," All Engineers Dinner of the American Power Conference, March 28, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Why Did it Happen Here?," Meadville Chamber of Commerce, May 25, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - [Remarks on the effects of Westinghouse Electric's IUE strike], Stone & Webster Dinner, June 2, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "The Coming Crisis in Education," Bucknell University Commencement, June 10, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "A Billion Dollar Ticket to the Future," Pacific Coast Electrical Association Conference, November 7, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - [Remarks at the dedication ceremonies of the Leslie Ann Hicks Power Station, Honolulu, Hawaii], November 9, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - [Outline of remarks on Westinghouse Electric's International Union of Electrical Workers (IUE) strike to unknown organization on West Coast], 1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "The Search for Future Scientists," Kansas City Chamber of Commerce, February 12, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "The Making and Marketing of Miracles," Electrical Association of Rochester, February 17, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Suggested remarks to the Allegheny Council, Boy Scouts of America, February 23, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "The Role of Marketing in the New American Economy," Presidents' Night Dinner of the Sales Executives Club, April 7, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Private Enterprise and the Private College," Birmingham-Southern College, Birmingham, Alabama, April 10, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Education for Self-Education," University of Pittsburgh, May 3, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "Looking Forward with Westinghouse During the Next Few Years," Stone & Webster Dinner, June 8, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "The Past is but a Prologue," Future Power Market Forum, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - [Remarks on Westinghouse Electric's progress in 1957 and outlook for 1958, likely to stockholders] (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Today's Sowing, Tomorrow's Harvest [on the future of the electrical industry]," Southwest Electric Conference, March 30, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - [Speech on the purpose of the Council for Financial Aid to Education and formal introductions of officers of the council], Duquesne Club, Pittsburgh, September 14, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - [Remarks on the Soviet threat to the United States], Annual Meeting of the Industrial Information Institute, October 21, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Remarks by Gwilym A. Price at the dinner held in his honor by the Chartiers Valley Services Club", November 16, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "What We Did - And What We Learned - In Rebuilding Pittsburgh," Annual Banquet of the Jackson, Mississippi Chamber of Commerce, January 5, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Legal Aspects of Atomic Energy," Pennsylvania Bar Association, February 2, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "What We Did - And What We Learned - In Rebuilding Pittsburgh," Better Business Bureau of Indianapolis, Indiana, April 26, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "What We Did - And What We Learned - In Rebuilding Pittsburgh," Businessmen's Luncheon at the Baker Hotel, Dallas, Texas, May 11, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Remarks at the Dedication Ceremonies of the Dan E. Kern Electric Plant of the Consumer's Power Company, Bay City, Michigan", June 22, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "The Relationship Between the University and the Industrial Society," Corporate Executives' Dinner, University of Rochester, NY, May 16, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - [Speech about the Modernization of the Electrical Industry], All-Electrical Industry Dinner, May 21, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Remarks at the Printing Week Banquet and [presentation of Dr. John C. Warner to receive] the Franklin Medallion Award", January 19, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "The Past is But a Prologue," Southeastern Electric Exchange Annual Meeting, March 26, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "The Problems and the Promises of the New Technological Age," on receiving the Progress Award of the American Society of Tool and Manufacturing Engineers, April 27, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Introduction of Admiral Ben Moreell, Metcalf Award Medalist," Engineer's Society of Western Pennsylvania Annual Banquet, February 3, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - "The Challenge of Greatness," Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry and American Institute of Architects, Chicago Chapter Honor Award Luncheon, April 9, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - "Opportunities in Electricity Through Innovation," Southwest Electric Conference, April 13, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - [Speech on Urban Renewal in Pittsburgh], Awards Dinner of the Design in Steel Award Program, February 4, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - [Speech reflecting on his life and career], University of Pittsburgh Law School Alumni Meeting, c1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- University of Pittsburgh, 1938-1975; IX.
  This series contains materials relating to Price's time on the Board of Trustees at the University of Pittsburgh, including newsclippings from Pittsburgh-area papers in the mid 1960s detailing the University's financial troubles and the resignation of Chancellor Edward Litchfield. Also programs from the Gwilym Price Engineering Lecture Series, including full text of lectures by Dr. Augustus Braun Kinzel (1968), Mr. Philip Sporn (1968), Dr. William R. Garrison (1969), and Dr. Eric A. Walker (1970), as well as an invitation to the lecture by Dr. James C. Fletcher (1974).
  - Appointment as instructor, newsclipping, c1938 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Newsclippings, December 1964-February 1965 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Newsclippings, March 1965-May 1965 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Newsclippings, June 1965 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Newsclippings, July 1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Newsclippings, August 1965 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - "Statement for Mr. Price to Fortune Magazine", c1967 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Gwilym Price Engineering Lecture Series, programs, 1968-1974 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Statement on University of Pittsburgh's mortgage loan, March 1975 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Westinghouse Electric, 1943-1973; X.
  This series contains materials relating to Price's career at Westinghouse, including extensive documentation of a trip that Price and other energy executives took to the former Soviet Union (USSR) in August 1958. Also includes limited materials related to George Ketchum, an advertising executive who worked on several of Westinghouse Electric's advertising campaigns.
  - Pittsburgh People's Trust Bank, congratulatory card, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Scrapbook: Dedication of Westinghouse Lamp Plant, Little Rock, Arkansas, January 12-13, 1950 (Box 13, Volume 1)
  - Business Reports and related materials, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Pamphlets and Programs, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Russia Trip: Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Russia Trip: Research Materials, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Russia Trip: Research Materials, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Russia Trip: Price's notes and itineraries, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Russia Trip: Russian-language materials, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Russia Trip: Reports, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Russia Trip: Press materials, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Russia Trip: Maps, c1958 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Russia Trip: U.S. Exchange, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence from Department of Justice, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Scrapbook: "Rebuilding Pittsburgh" at Akron Chamber of Commerce, February 1960 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Scrapbook: Westinghouse Standard Control Division Supervisors Dinner Meeting, March 18, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - "On the Occasion of Miss J. Aguirre's 25th Anniversary with Westinghouse," speech by J. de Cubas, President, Westinghouse Electric International Co., September 25, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - George Ketchum, 1971-75 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Price's Westinghouse stock summary, April 13, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Bettis Atomic Power Laboratory Technology Night Presentation, December 10-11, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Oversized materials, 1946-1983; XI.
  - Political Cartoon about Sen. Hugh Scott by Cy Hungerford, signed by Scott, 1962 (Box O/S 15, Folder 1)
  - Political Cartoon about Sen. Hugh Scott, signed by Scott, 1970 (Box O/S 15, Folder 2)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, Westinghouse Order of Merit, September 18, 1946 (Box O/S 15, Folder 3)
  - Republican Sens. Jake Garn, Hal Kahn, Ted Stevens, John Tower, Strom Thurmond, Dick Lugar, and Jim McClure, photograph signed by all with inscription to Price., c1980 (Box O/S 15, Folder 4)
  - M.I.T. Corporation Annual Meeting, photograph, September 26, 1980 (Box O/S 15, Folder 5)
  - M.I.T. Corporation Annual Meeting, photograph, October 7, 1983 (Box O/S 15, Folder 6)
  - "Three Generations of Westinghouse Chairmen" poster., c1981 (Box O/S 15, Folder 7)
  - Westinghouse, Stockholders' meeting, image, 1953 (Box O/S 15, Folder 8)
- Photographs, 1957-1983; XII.
  Series contains photographs from Price's business career, including trips with Westinghouse, as well as photographs from his personal life and leisure time. Photo albums document visits with other Westinghouse and energy industry executives to South Africa, where Price met with executives from ISCOR (now ArcelorMittal) and FWJ Industries, Japan, likely when Price received the Patent of Decoration for the Third Class of the Order of the Rising Sun, China, where Price visited with executives of the China Power System, and Russia, where Price and other energy executives toured Moscow and other locations related to the country's energy infrastructure. There are also several sets of photographs and one small album documenting Price's trips to Anacosti Island (Canada), Copper River (Alaska), Iceland, Deep Water Cay (Bahamas), and other unidentified locations.
  - Professional life, 1957-1983; 1.
    Subseries largely contains photographs from Price's time at Westinghouse, particularly from overseas trips and meetings, and one set of photographs from the dedication of Bevier Engineering Library at the University of Pittsburgh.
    - Westinghouse Board of Directors meeting, April 15, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Westinghouse Russia Trip Photo Album, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Printing Week Banquet, Medallion Award acceptance, January 19, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Television appearance, c 1960 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Bevier Engineering Library Dedication, February 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, Dinner honoring Alva Lula Brush, May 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)